Guide to the Harry Adams Photographs
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Identified Subjects, 1951–1985
  - Politicians and Political Events
    - Bradley, Tom
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with another man, circa 1975 (Box 6, Folder 311)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with two men, circa 1975; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 312)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with two men, circa 1975 (Box 6, Folder 313)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with three men, 1976 January 20 (Box 6, Folder 314)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with a woman, 1977 April (Box 6, Folder 315)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with four women and three men, circa 1977 (Box 6, Folder 316)
      - Interior view of Tom Bradley at a pulpit in a church, circa 1977 (Box 6, Folder 317)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with H. Claude Hudson and Paul R. Williams with recognition certificates of their day in Los Angeles, California, at a meeting of the Senior Raggers at the 38th Street Young Men's Christian Association building, circa 1979; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 318)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with a woman and a man, 1980 September (Box 6, Folder 319)
      - Exterior view of a man speaking at a microphone and Tom Bradley, Kenneth Hahn, and Charles Lloyd sitting nearby, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 320)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley and Gilbert William Lindsay with three men, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 321)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with a girl and boy, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 322)
        Inscription on recto by Bradley to "Victor"
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with a group around a table, probably at a banquet, consisting of twelve women and five men, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 323)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with his hand lifted by another man, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 324)
      - Interior portraits of Tom Bradley with a group that includes a woman dressed in a white bejeweled costume, circa 1980; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 325)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley and a woman, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 326)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley and a woman, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 327)
      - Exterior portrait of Tom Bradley with a woman and six men, 1981 September (Box 6, Folder 328)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley presenting the key to the City of Los Angeles to a man with a woman nearby, 1985 April; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 329)
      - Interior portraits of Tom Bradley with three men, 1985 May; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 330)
      - Group portraits of men, including Tom Bradley and Gilbert William Lindsay, 1985 June; 5 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - Brooke, Edward W. (Edward William)
      - Interior portraits and views related to a banquet for Edward W. (Edward William) Brooke at the Los Angeles Biltmore Hotel, including portraits of Brooke and Billy Mills, 1967 February 10; 8 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - Brown, Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald)
      - Interior portrait of Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald) Brown, 1961 October 21 (Box 6, Folder 333)
      - Interior view of a man at a podium flanked by three men and Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald) Brown seated behind them at the Los Angeles Biltmore Hotel, 1962 March 3-4 (Box 6, Folder 334)
      - Exterior views of Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald) Brown and J. "Jake" Lopez, candidate for the 55th Assembly District, in Compton, California, 1964 May 7; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 335)
      - Interior portraits of Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald) Brown, 1965 September 16; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 336)
      - Interior portrait of Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald) Brown with others at an event, circa 1965; 3 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 337)
      - Interior and exterior portraits of Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald) Brown with supporters, 1966 May 7; 5 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 338)
      - Interior portrait of Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald) Brown with a woman, 1966 May 8 (Box 6, Folder 339)
      - Interior portraits for a dinner for Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald) Brown, including images of Brown, Milton Berle, Hubert Humphrey, Helen Smith, and Sherman Smith, 1966 September 26; 9 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 340)
    - Brown, Jerry
      - Interior view of Jerry Brown addressing a group at the Hyatt Regency, Los Angeles, California, 1973 August 12 (Box 6, Folder 341)
      - Interior portrait of Jerry Brown and a woman, probably in the classified advertising department of the Los Angeles Sentinel newspaper, circa 1973 (Box 6, Folder 342)
      - Interior views of Jerry Brown and Tom Bradley during the primary elections during the 1974 California gubernatorial election, 1974 June 4; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 343)
      - Exterior view of Jerry Brown with a group of children, probably at an event honoring Martin Luther King, Jr., 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 344)
      - Exterior view of Jerry Brown with constituents at events, circa 1977; 4 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 345)
      - Exterior portraits of Jerry Brown with a woman and two men as well as with a woman, circa 1980; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 346)
      - Interior portrait of Jerry Brown holding a newspaper, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 347)
      - Interior portrait of Jerry Brown with two women and a man, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 348)
    - Brown, Willie L. (Willie Lewis)
      - Interior portrait of three men, including Willie L. (Willie Lewis) Brown, with an award given to the Westinghouse Electric Corporation by the National Black Caucus of State Legislators, 1984 November 30 (Box 6, Folder 349)
      - Interior portrait of Willie L. (Willie Lewis) Brown with five men at a meeting of the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People in San Fernando, 1985 June (Box 6, Folder 350)
    - Bunche, Ralph Johnson
      - Interior portrait of Ralph Johnson Bunche and two men at a podium, 1966 May 15 (Box 6, Folder 351)
    - Burke, Yvonne Brathwaite
      - Views of Yvonne Brathwaite (later Burke) and Rosalind Miles riding in a convertible automobiles during a parade in Los Angeles, California, 1972 August; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 352)
      - Interior portrait of four women, including Yvonne Brathwaite (later Burke), and a man, probably at a Progressive Californians, Los Angeles Chapter, banquet, 1973 May (Box 6, Folder 353)
    - Carter, Jimmy
      - Interior portrait of Jimmy Carter with Kenneth Hahn and another man in the foreground of a larger group, 1976 June (Box 7, Folder 354)
      - Exterior views of preparations for the inauguration of Jimmy Carter, including views of the United States Capitol Building as well as the gates to the White House, 1977 January 19; 7 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 355)
      - Interior and exterior views of attendees at an inauguration of Jimmy Carter event in Washington, D.C., which includes a views of Walter Mondale and Joan Mondale addressing attendees, 1977 January 20; 18 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 356)
    - Carter, Rosalyn
      - Exterior portraits of Rosalynn Carter, Ethel Arnold Bradley, Diane Watson, and others, 1976 September 14; 2 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 357)
      - Interior portrait of Rosalynn Carter and a woman named Blanche, circa 1976 (Box 7, Folder 358)
    - Cranston, Alan
      - Interior portrait of Alan Cranston and Bill Love, circa 1970 (Box 7, Folder 359)
      - Interior views from an event, including Alan Cranston, Gilbert William Lindsay, and John V. (John Varick) Tunney, 1975 January 3; 3 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 360)
    - Democratic Party in California
      - Interior view of two male members of the California delegation of the Democratic Party at the Los Angeles International Airport, 1964 August (Box 7, Folder 361)
      - Interior portraits of individuals and groups related to the California Democratic Party, including a view of an information table for the United Farmworkers of America, 1966 January 16; 28 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 362)
    - Dymally, Mervyn M.
      - Interior portrait of Mervyn M. Dymally and Sidney Poitier with a resolution from the California Legislative Assembly commending Poitier, 1964 April (Box 7, Folder 363)
      - Interior views of Mervyn M. Dymally, Gilbert William Lindsay, Pierre Salinger, Billy Mills, and F. Douglas Ferrell, 1964 April; 2 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 364)
      - Exterior portrait of Mervyn M. Dymally, F. Douglas Ferrell and Gilbert William Lindsay at Conference of the Unemployed held at Wrigley Field, Los Angeles, California, 1964 May 21 (Box 7, Folder 365)
      - Exterior portrait of five men including Mervyn M. Dymally, Douglas Ferrell, Gilbert William Lindsay, Billy Mills, and Pierre Salinger, circa 1964 (Box 7, Folder 366)
      - Interior portraits at a banquet, including a portraits of Mervyn M. Dymally, Doostie Williams, Elizabeth Yorty, and Sam Yorty, 1966 March 4-5; 6 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 367)
      - Interior portraits related to a birthday celebration for Mervyn M. Dymally including Dymally with groups and individuals including Billy Mills and Sidney Poitier, 1967 May 12; 16 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 368)
      - Interior portrait of Mervyn M. Dymally and a woman holding an award for Earl Caldwell in recognition of his contribution to community and public affairs, 1970 September 18; 2 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 369)
      - Interior portrait of a woman and seven men, including Mervyn M. Dymally, Gilbert William Lindsay, and Billy Mills, circa 1970 (Box 7, Folder 370)
      - Interior portraits at a reception of the Black Media of California at the home of Mervyn M. Dymally, including a portraits of Dymally, Hubert Humphrey, and Edward "Abie" Robinson, 1971 October 16; 3 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 371)
      - Interior portrait of Mervyn M. Dymally and Gilbert William Lindsay with a woman and three men, 1975 August; 2 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 372)
    - Engle, Clair
      - Interior portrait of Clair Engle and two women, probably during his campaign for United States Senator, 1958 February (Box 7, Folder 373)
    - Hahn, Kenneth
      - Exterior view of a groundbreaking, possibly for the Martin Luther King Jr. County Hospital, with a group that includes Kenneth Hahn, circa 1968 (Box 7, Folder 374)
      - Exterior portraits of a group, including Kenneth Hahn, Gilbert William Lindsay, and Charles Earl Lloyd, contributing money to a construction helmet, 1976 September; 3 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 375)
    - Hawkins, Augustus F.
      - Interior view of Augustus F. Hawkins addressing a group, circa 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 376)
      - Interior portraits of an event honoring Augustus F. Hawkins, including portraits of Hawkins and Jerry Brown, 1982 February 5-6; 5 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 377)
      - Interior portrait of Augustus F. Hawkins holding an award and with a woman and two men, circa 1982 (Box 7, Folder 378)
      - Interior portrait of Augustus F. Hawkins with a woman and a man, 1985 June (Box 7, Folder 379)
    - Henning, John F.
      - Interior portrait of John F. Henning with two women, circa 1964 (Box 7, Folder 380)
    - Humphrey, Hubert
      - Exterior view of a voter registration rally for Hubert Humphrey, 1968 July 27 (Box 7, Folder 381)
      - Exterior view of James Brown endorsing Hubert Humphrey for President of the United States in the Watts neighborhood of Los Angeles, California, 1968 July 29 (Box 7, Folder 382)
      - Exterior views at a campaign event for Hubert Humphrey, which include Sam Yorty, 1968; 8 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 383)
      - Interior portraits at a campaign event for Hubert Humphrey, which include Gilbert William Lindsay, 1968; 4 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 384)
      - Interior views at a campaign event for Hubert Humphrey, which include Humphrey signing photographic prints, 1968; 3 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 385)
      - Copy photograph of the seal of the Vice President of the United States, circa 1968 (Box 7, Folder 386)
      - Interior portrait of Hubert Humphrey with two men, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 387)
    - Jackson, Jesse
      - Exterior view of Jesse Jackson addressing a crowd, 1968 August 5 (Box 7, Folder 388)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B.
      - Interior views of an Equal Employment Opportunities event at the Ambassador Hotel in Los Angeles, California, attended by Lyndon B. Johnson and Gilbert William Lindsay, 1963 November 14; 4 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 389)
      - Exterior portraits at a campaign events for Lyndon B. Johnson, including images of Johnson and Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald) Brown, 1964 August; 10 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 390)
    - Jones, James E.
      - Interior portrait of a woman and a man at a political event for James E. Jones, candidate for the Los Angeles Board of Education, 1965 February (Box 7, Folder 391)
    - Kennedy, Edward M. (Edward Moore)
      - Interior portrait of Edward M. (Edward Moore) Kennedy with two women and two men, 1981 May 2 (Box 7, Folder 392)
    - Kennedy, John F.
      - Exterior view of John F. Kennedy, Lyndon B. Johnson, and Hubert H. Humphrey at the Los Angeles Coliseum during the Democratic Party Convention, 1960 July 16 (Box 7, Folder 393)
      - Exterior views of John F. Kennedy with supporters at events at the 5400 block of Crenshaw Boulevard, Los Angeles, California, 1960 November 1; 2 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 394)
      - Interior views of John F. Kennedy with supporters, probably at the Elks Auditorium, Los Angeles, California, 1960 November 1; 4 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 395)
      - Interior portrait of five women with bumper stickers and sign supporting the election John F. Kennedy and Lyndon B. Johnson, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 396)
      - Interior views of a breakfast in honor of John F. Kennedy given by Democratic State Committeewomen of California at the Hollywood Palladium, Los Angeles, 1963 June 8; 2 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 397)
      - Exterior view of John F. Kennedy with supporters in Los Angeles, California, 1963 June 8? (Box 7, Folder 398)
    - Kennedy, Robert F.
      - Interior portrait of Robert F. Kennedy with a man and woman at a banquet at the Ambassador Hotel, Los Angeles, California, 1965 November 5 (Box 7, Folder 399)
      - Interior and exterior views at a campaign events for Robert F. Kennedy, which include photographer Howard Bingham, Mervyn M. Dymally, Booker Griffin, Jr., and Billy Mills, 1968 March 25; 13 photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 400)
      - Exterior portrait of five women and a man with a sign and hats supporting the Robert F. Kennedy, 1968 March (Box 7, Folder 401)
    - Lindsay, Gilbert William
      - Exterior portraits of a group visiting sites in Los Angeles, including Wrigley Field; group includes Gilbert William Lindsay and Billy Mills, 1965 June 14; 6 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 402)
      - Exterior portrait of Gilbert William Lindsay with two women and five men, circa 1965 (Box 8, Folder 403)
      - Interior portrait of Gilbert William Lindsay with two women, circa 1965 (Box 8, Folder 404)
      - Interior portrait of a man wearing a turban and clip-on earrings, possibly a member of a fraternal order, with others including Gilbert William Lindsay and Willie Brown, 1973 June; 4 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 405)
      - Interior portrait of six men, including Gilbert William Lindsay and Billy Mills, 1973 October (Box 8, Folder 406)
      - Interior portraits at an banquet that include Gilbert William Lindsay and Billy Mills, 1973 November; 6 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 407)
      - Interior portrait of Gilbert William Lindsay with four girls, three boys, a woman, and a man, 1975 February 1 (Box 8, Folder 408)
      - Interior portraits at an event that include Gilbert William Lindsay and others, 1975 February 16; 3 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 409)
      - Interior portraits of Gilbert William Lindsay and six women, 1975 March; 2 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 410)
      - Interior portrait of Gilbert William Lindsay with two women and a man, 1976 August (Box 8, Folder 411)
      - Interior portrait of Gilbert William Lindsay with four men, circa 1980 (Box 8, Folder 412)
      - Exterior portrait of a woman and eleven men at a garden project sponsored by Gilbert William Lindsay, 1981 December (Box 8, Folder 413)
      - Interior portrait of Gilbert William Lindsay with two women and five men at an event, circa 1982 (Box 8, Folder 414)
      - Interior portrait of Gilbert William Lindsay with a woman and a man as well as a proclamation of Canadian Club Day in Los Angeles, California, 1985 April (Box 8, Folder 415)
    - McFarlin, Emma Daniels
      - Interior views related to the appointment of Emma Daniels McFarlin as government liaison for the Los Angeles Olympic Organizing Committee including images of McFarlin and Peter V. Ueberroth with others, 1981 October 29; 14 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 416)
        Accompanied by a press release and folder from the event
    - Mills, Billy
      - Studio portrait of Billy Mills, 1963 October (Box 8, Folder 417)
    - Murrell, Cecil B.
      - Interior portrait of Cecil B. Murrell and twenty supporters during his campaign for the California State Senate from District 39, 1966 October 28 (Box 8, Folder 418)
    - Progressive Californians
      - Interior portrait of a woman and a man at a Progressive Californians, Los Angeles Chapter, banquet honoring Yvonne Brathwaite Burke, 1967 April 22 (Box 8, Folder 419)
      - Interior portrait of four women and a man at a banquet for the Progressive Californians, Los Angeles Chapter, 1973 December (Box 8, Folder 420)
      - Interior portrait of two men at a meeting of the Progressive Californians, Los Angeles Chapter, 1975 April (Box 8, Folder 421)
    - Reagan, Ronald
      - Interior views of Gilbert William Lindsay, Ronald Reagan, and Sam Yorty, with others at an event, 1970 November 23; 3 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 422)
      - Interior portraits of Ronald Reagan with others, including Tom Bradley, Willis Carson, and Daniel W. Spaulding, during the annual meeting of the National Association of Real Estate Brokers at the Los Angeles Biltmore Hotel, 1973 August 12-17; 3 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 423)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
      - Interior view of Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich) Rockefeller with supporters, 1964 March (Box 8, Folder 424)
    - Salinger, Pierre
      - Interior portrait of Pierre Salinger with Elbert T. Hudson and a boy and a man, 1964 May (Box 8, Folder 425)
    - Shriver, Sargent
      - Views of Sargent Shriver with adults and children, 1966 June 13; 6 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 426)
      - Views of Sergeant Shriver and parade in the Westminster neighborhood of Watts in South Central Los Angeles, California, as part of an "inspection tour of Los Angeles' anti-poverty projects", 1966 August 14; 2 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 427)
    - Tinglof, Mary
      - Exterior portrait of Mary Tinglof and Dan Blocker, as well as a woman and a man, 1965 February (Box 8, Folder 428)
    - Tunney, John V. (John Varick)
      - Exterior portrait of John V. (John Varick) Tunney with a large group of women and men, circa 1970 (Box 8, Folder 429)
      - Interior portrait of John V. (John Varick) Tunney with four women, 1976 October (Box 8, Folder 430)
    - Weaver, Fred
      - Interior portrait of a group involved in the election campaign of Fred Weaver to the Los Angeles Board of Education consisting of eight women and eleven men, circa 1962 (Box 8, Folder 431)
    - Yorty, Sam
      - Interior view of Sam Yorty at a podium at the Statler Hotel, Los Angeles, California, 1964 January (Box 8, Folder 432)
      - Interior view of Sam Yorty at microphone, probably at Los Angeles City Hall, 1965 January (Box 8, Folder 433)
      - Interior portrait of Sam Yorty presenting a card to a man with another man nearby, probably at the Los Angeles City Hall, circa 1965 (Box 8, Folder 434)
      - Interior portraits of Sam Yorty presenting certificates of appreciation to Cliff Hall, James Rodney Smith, and another man, 1968 April; 3 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 435)
    - Washington, Harold
      - Interior portrait of Harold Washington and a man, 1983 March 19 (Box 8, Folder 436)
  - Sites in California
    - Avalon Boulevard, Los Angeles
      - Exterior view of three women and three men, including a clergyman, walking on Avalon Boulevard, Los Angeles, California, 1966 May 16 (Box 8, Folder 437)
    - Central City Community Mental Health Facility
      - Views of the Central City Community Mental Health Facility in Los Angeles, California, 1973 November; 2 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 438)
    - Community Services Center
      - Exterior view of the Community Services Center in Willowbrook, California, 1974 November (Box 8, Folder 439)
    - Continental Meat Company
      - Views related to the grand opening of the Continental Meat Company, 1967 April 25; 2 photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 440)
    - Golden Valley
      - View of a sign for Golden Valley, a retirement center for the Improved Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks of the World in Mira Loma, California, 1966 May 8 (Box 8, Folder 441)
    - Los Angeles City Hall
      - Interior portrait of two men looking at a large bas relief in the Los Angeles City Hall, 1967 February 5 (Box 8, Folder 442)
    - Skatium
      - Interior portrait of a large group, which includes Howard Cantonwine, Jack Wachs, and Al Pops, at the grand opening of Skatium, a roller skating rink, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 443)
  - Sites and Events Outside California
    - Bahamas
      - Interior portraits and exterior views related to a travel agent conference sponsored by Inside Travel News in Freeport and Nassau, Bahamas, 1975 September 16-21; 39 photographic prints (Box 9, Folder 444)
    - Cruise Ship
      - Exterior portrait of seven women on a cruise ship with men skeet shooting in the background, 1981 April (Box 9, Folder 445)
    - Fiji+D943
      - Exterior and interior views related to tourist activities at Fiji, 1978 June; 16 photographic prints (Box 9, Folder 446)
      - Exterior views related to a hot stone walking at Fiji, 1978 June; 25 photographic prints (Box 9, Folder 447)
      - Exterior views related to firing pottery at Fiji, 1978 June; 7 photographic prints (Box 9, Folder 448)
    - Hawaii
      - Views of a visit to Hawaii, including and exterior view of six men arriving at an airport and an interior portrait of five men with one man holding a guitar, 1972 November; 2 photographic prints (Box 9, Folder 449)
    - Kenya
      - Interior view of Desmond Tutu at a pulpit surrounded by people in Nairobi, Kenya, 1985 May (Box 9, Folder 450)
      - View of a statue of Jomo Kenyatta by James Butler and the Kenyatta International Convention Centre, Nairobi, Kenya, 1985 May (Box 9, Folder 451)
    - Las Vegas, Nevada
      - Exterior view of the 100 block of Fremont Street, Las Vegas, Nevada, with casinos including the Golden Nugget, Fremont, and Horseshoe, 1964 June; 2 photographic prints (Box 9, Folder 452)
      - View of a crowd at the MGM Grand Hotel in Las Vegas, Nevada, its grand opening night with celebrities, including Barbara Eden, Fred MacMurray, and Jane Powell, 1973 December 5; 6 photographic prints (Box 9, Folder 453)
      - Interior view of Dean Martin performing on stage probably at the MGM Grand Hotel and Casino, 1973 December (Box 9, Folder 454)
      - Exterior of the MGM Grand Hotel and Casino, including Fountains and statuary in front of the porte-cochere, as well as construction workers, circa 1973 (Box 9, Folder 455)